PERLA PEREZ - ORONA

perlap156@gmail.com • 404.809.5728

CAREER PROFILE

Hard-working developer skilled in conceptualizing and delivering elegant, user-centered solutions effectively and efficiently. 4+ years of experience in front-end languages such as HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Skilled at writing well-designed, testable and efficient code using current best practices in web development. A regular attendee of web developer meetups.

Github: https://github.com/perlap156

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/perla-perez-orona-07221394/

Website: https://perlaperezorona.com/

EDUCATION

University of Texas at Arlington B.A. Communications of Technology Graduated In 2018

SKILLS

HTML

CSS3

SASS

JS

BootStrap

PHP

MySQL

WordPress

Axure

Adobe Creative Suite

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front- End Developer Elevation Ads

Oct 2018 - Present

- Developed websites using Wordpress and modified existing codes as needed.
- Designed websites using the mobile-first approach, while executing the client's website goals and creating a user friendly experience.
- · Communicated with clients during the overall website building process.

Web Developer Freelancer Self- Employed

Aug 2017- Sept 2018

- · Consulted with clients to outline website goals, illustrate wire frame, and site functionality.
- Developed a user-friendly architecture by programming site navigation, social media links, and organizing site content into a logical catalog.
- · Developed responsive designs and tested with browserstack.

Communication Intern Refugee Services of Texas

Aug 2016 - July 2017

- · Sent mass emails to volunteers using Mail Chimp.
- Managed and designed volunteer newsletter for volunteer opportunities.
- · Maintained their social media accounts.